https://store.sundancesolar.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Wish Lists
View Cart (0)
Categories
For Teachers Only!
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.· Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.· We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.· We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.· We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.· Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.· We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.· We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.RETURN POLICY You may return any item within 30 days. No need to explain. We will pay return shipping if we sent the wrong order or item is received damaged. Buyer pays return shipping if you have changed your mind or simply want an exchange. You should expect to receive your refund within 1-3 business days of us receiving the item. Refund will be given in the same way it was received Check,Debit or Credit Card.
New Products
SunBender 2 LED Solar Light Kit - Pre-wired
$19.95
Add to Compare
Add to Wishlist
Add To Cart
Solar Buzzy Bug Classroom Pack - 25 Pre-wired Kits
$188.00
Copyright 2020 Sundance Solar . All Rights Reserved.  Sitemap |
Bigcommerce Premium Themes by PSDCenter
All prices are in USD.
Close
Close
Selected For Comparision
Compare Now
